

Pranjali Verma

Pranjali Verma

Sample Samp

Goal-Oriented Developer with Experience in Frontend technologies like React JS and Next JS. I am living, learning and leveling up one day at a time.

I am enthusiastic, responsible and hard working Software Engineer with experience in React JS, Next JS and other frontend technologies. I am exploring and enhancing my technical knowledge to build fully functional responsive web designs.

Skills: **API Integration** React JS HTML 5 CSS 3 Next Js JavaScript **JQuery API Integration** GitHub SASS/LESS **Bootstrap** Bitbuckit Figma **DBMS** MySQL C/C++

# Experience

AurigalT aurigait.com

Oct 2020 to Present

- Associate Software Enginner Jaipur, Rajasthan, India
- I am working as a Frontend Developer on React JS, Next JS and other frontend technologies to build Responsive Web Designs.
- I value simple content structure, clean design patterns, and thoughtful interactions.
- Collaborating with cross-functional teams to define, design, and ship new features.
- Performing Unit testing of code for robustness, including edge cases, usability, and general reliability.
- Working on bug fixing and improving application performance.
- Continuously discovering, evaluating, and implementing new technologies to maximize development efficiency.
- Developing components which are SEO friendly.
- Working with popular React JS workflows (such as redux).

#### North Western Railways

May 2019 to Jun 2019

Intern Trainee Jaipur

I worked on some of the most powerful machines on the planet at Signal and Control Department and understand how automation of gadgets and their logics plays a vital role in resources management at big level.

## Education

Swami Keshvanand Institute of Technology, Management & Gramothan , Jaipur

Jun 2016 to Dec 2020

Btech, ECE (Honours), RTU, Kota

St. Anselm Sr. Sec. School , Jaipur stanselmsmns.ac.in

Apr 2015 to Apr 2016

12th, PCM IP (76.2%), CBSE

St. Anselm Sr. Sec. School, Jaipur stanselmsmns.ac.in

Apr 2013 to Apr 2014

10th, (CGPA: 8.4), CBSE

# **Projects**

### CaterHero

**13.71.24.145/** 

Designed and built advanced applications using React JS and Next JS. Collaborated with cross-functional teams to define, design, and ship new features. Done Unit testing of code for robustness, including edge cases, usability, and general reliability. Worked on bug fixing and improving application performance. Continuously discovered, evaluated, and implemented new technologies to maximize development efficiency. Worked with popular React JS workflows (such as redux). Developed components which are SEO friendly.

Github, Bitbucket, Next JS, Redux, React JS, Zeplin, Sass, Hooks

### **Table Tennis App - Dummy Project**

**139.59.16.180:5002/** 

Developed feature sets that involve Responsive UIs and Restful API and ensure a seamless experience. Developed interactive, user-friendly applications using the latest frameworks. Assured that all user input is validated before submitting to back-end using React packages. Built reusable code and libraries for future use. Translated storyboards and use cases into functional applications.

Github, Hooks, Figma, BitBucket, Putty, JavaScript, React Js

### Admin Dashboard - Dummy Project

Worked experience with React JS and ES6 and got thorough understanding of its core principles. Got the knowledge of preprocessors like SASS/LESS, CSS-Modules. Got up-to-date, in-depth knowledge of modern web technologies HTML5, JavaScript, JQuery and Bootstrap.

JavaScript, Class Components, Redux, React JS

	rengths ——————————————————————
(	ood Communication Skills $) ($ Creative $) ($ Goal Oriented $) ($ Leadership Skills $) ($ Optimistic $)$